[{"answer": "Put the seatbelt on, buddy, because it's going to be a bumpy ride.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 14, "question": "If I was Justin Bieber, what would you say?", "qSentId": 13}, {"answer": "Oh, yes, I tried it.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 17, "question": "You've admitted to one dose of Botox?", "qSentId": 16}, {"answer": "It's so cool.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 29, "question": "Do they really?", "qSentId": 28}, {"answer": "It's an ego builder, let me tell you.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 36, "question": "It must still give you even you guys a buzz, isn't it?", "qSentId": 35}, {"answer": "If you're ever feeling bad about yourself, you just drive past the Flamingo and it's like the biggest billboard in the city.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 38, "question": "Is it?", "qSentId": 37}, {"answer": "No, I mean, you know, you think about a career.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 40, "question": "Did you ever imagine in the '70s when you started that show, did you ever imagine that here you'd be 40 years later doing this in Vegas?", "qSentId": 39}, {"answer": "It just happened the other night.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 69, "question": "And it's nice to be out there with somebody who they can tell if something's not working and they're there to cover each other or whatever it is, you know?", "qSentId": 68}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 79, "question": "You can completely trust each other?", "qSentId": 78}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 84, "question": "Whoever else you work with?", "qSentId": 83}, {"answer": "I don't know if I speak on behalf of Marie, but when we put this show together, you could throw as much money as you want at a show.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 120, "question": "What's the thing that takes you to that level?", "qSentId": 119}, {"answer": "We did --", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 133, "question": "What are you laughing at?", "qSentId": 132}, {"answer": "Don't go into that.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 137, "question": "We did QVC the other day, OK?", "qSentId": 136}, {"answer": "Learning from old school.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 150, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 149}, {"answer": "But who would you like to --", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 158, "question": "You know?", "qSentId": 157}, {"answer": "We did.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 166, "question": "Who of all the greats that played in Vegas mould you most like to have seen in a theater like this?", "qSentId": 165}, {"answer": "We worked with them.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 169, "question": "You saw them all?", "qSentId": 168}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 178, "question": "Did you perform with Sasha and Sinatra?", "qSentId": 177}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 181, "question": "And Sammy Davis?", "qSentId": 180}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 184, "question": "Dean Martin?", "qSentId": 183}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 187, "question": "Elvis?", "qSentId": 186}, {"answer": "Lucille Ball.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 190, "question": "Elvis in Vegas?", "qSentId": 189}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 245, "question": "So being a proper star, really, from what you're saying is, look out to an audience and making them feel as important as they're making you feel?", "qSentId": 244}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 257, "question": "Do you remember what Groucho Marx did to you?", "qSentId": 256}, {"answer": "Groucho Marx.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 262, "question": "Groucho Marx?", "qSentId": 261}, {"answer": "He was on the \"Donny and Marie Show\" and -- yes.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 268, "question": "Serious?", "qSentId": 267}, {"answer": "John Wayne was a very stoic man.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 285, "question": "What was John Wayne like?", "qSentId": 284}, {"answer": "He was John Wayne.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 291, "question": "He talked like this really, you know?", "qSentId": 290}, {"answer": "Sir, you cannot imagine how glad I am to see you.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 316, "question": "Why does the maiden who keeps a crackling fire on such a frosty day?", "qSentId": 315}, {"answer": "Well, because you got married to a guy you married before.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 323, "question": "That's the most exciting thing?", "qSentId": 322}, {"answer": "Well --", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 326, "question": "Tell me how did -- how did this happen?", "qSentId": 325}, {"answer": "It's been 29 years.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 328, "question": "You got married how long ago?", "qSentId": 327}, {"answer": "You know, Piers, I think too young.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 336, "question": "What was -- what was wrong then?", "qSentId": 335}, {"answer": "No, he never remarried, no.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 346, "question": "You remarried, but he never did, is that right?", "qSentId": 345}, {"answer": "So you were a single woman, and he was a single guy.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 360, "question": "Oh, yes, I'd been divorced almost, what, six years now or something like that?", "qSentId": 359}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 367, "question": "Did your son know that you were dating?", "qSentId": 366}, {"answer": "When we told him we were getting married.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "How long did you keep it from him?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 372, "question": "Seriously?", "qSentId": 371}, {"answer": "He's 28.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 393, "question": "And your son is, what, nearly 30 now?", "qSentId": 392}, {"answer": "I thought it was fantastic.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 398, "question": "What was your reaction?", "qSentId": 397}, {"answer": "Let's go one step further, it's always been uncomfortable between -- at least for me, between us, that I have a very successful marriage for 33 years and she didn't.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 406, "question": "I mean, for any brother, when you see a sister have her heartbroken as you said you did the first time when the marriage fell apart, doesn't part of you feel that protective thing, I hope this doesn't happen again with this guy?", "qSentId": 405}, {"answer": "You know, the only thing I can say is when it's right, it's really right.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 429, "question": "Was there a moment?", "qSentId": 428}, {"answer": "I just think I'm a hard habit to break.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 435, "question": "Do you think that?", "qSentId": 434}, {"answer": "It was beautiful.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 470, "question": "When you saw yourself -- and what did you think, Donny, when you saw her in that dress again?", "qSentId": 469}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 474, "question": "Did you get it?", "qSentId": 473}, {"answer": "Well, actually a sort of serious thing, actually.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 486, "question": "What do you want to talk to me about?", "qSentId": 485}, {"answer": "No, I want you to stay.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 488, "question": "Shall I leave?", "qSentId": 487}, {"answer": "No, I chose it deliberately.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 495, "question": "Did you choose that day deliberately or was it just a freak coincidence?", "qSentId": 494}, {"answer": "Yes, completely, I get that.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 510, "question": "You know?", "qSentId": 509}, {"answer": "Oh, that would have been something my mother -- yes.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 517, "question": "Would she have been happy, your mom?", "qSentId": 516}, {"answer": "And put Michael's picture.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 528, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 527}, {"answer": "You never get over that.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 540, "question": "What's the reality?", "qSentId": 539}, {"answer": "Well, you know, God says you go through the sorrow to know the joys.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 557, "question": "It's just the worst parental nightmare, isn't it?", "qSentId": 556}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 570, "question": "You did?", "qSentId": 569}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 572, "question": "You felt his presence on your wedding day?", "qSentId": 571}, {"answer": "You can only imagine what we went through here at the Flamingo.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 578, "question": "Donny, what was it like for to you see your sister go through such a crushing tragedy and be working with her at the same time?", "qSentId": 577}, {"answer": "I think you've got to be careful about that, Piers.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 589, "question": "Is it a way of getting back into your life?", "qSentId": 588}, {"answer": "You know, everybody will have their reasons for doing things.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 602, "question": "Did you draw a great comfort from the audience reaction?", "qSentId": 601}, {"answer": "Well, you know, he could tell I was hurting.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 631, "question": "When you say Donny was your rock, in what way?", "qSentId": 630}, {"answer": "I remember when you asked me this question.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 640, "question": "When we come back, I want to talk to you about the door marked fame that you two were shoved through when you were very young?", "qSentId": 639}, {"answer": "Oh, Piers, Piers, Piers.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 643, "question": "Would still want to go through that?", "qSentId": 642}, {"answer": "Every girl I got my eye on, age -- I don't know -- nine or 10, didn't want to know because she had Donny bloody Osmond on her wall.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 650, "question": "Oh, the Osmonds, the other ones?", "qSentId": 649}, {"answer": "Yes, I do.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 663, "question": "Do you remember when the balconies collapsed from the weight?", "qSentId": 662}, {"answer": "If I could have it the way I have it at this very moment, I would walk through that door.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 681, "question": "If I could take you back to the door marked fame and give you the option not to go through that, to lead a completely normal, anonymous life, without everything that fame brings, would you take that option?", "qSentId": 680}, {"answer": "He's going through so much heartache.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 687, "question": "What he's going to go through?", "qSentId": 686}, {"answer": "No, I love -- I was just about to say, I've gone through many, many doors where I have actually made full circle and I've embraced \"Puppy Love\" to where I absolutely enjoy singing that song.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 691, "question": "Do you still hate \"Puppy Love\"?", "qSentId": 690}, {"answer": "Yes, it was a millstone.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 695, "question": "There be have moments in your career when \"Puppy Love\" has been this massive millstone around your neck, hasn't it?", "qSentId": 694}, {"answer": "He's got it now.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 698, "question": "Is it inevitable?", "qSentId": 697}, {"answer": "Put the seat belt on, buddy, because it's going to be a bumpy ride.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 704, "question": "If I was Justin Bieber, what would you say?", "qSentId": 703}, {"answer": "Well, I had to wait until she stopped playing with dolls.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 749, "question": "What finally brought you back to recording?", "qSentId": 748}, {"answer": "Well, you know -- I don't know fun is the right word.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 753, "question": "Was it fun?", "qSentId": 752}, {"answer": "Oh, you know, I think initially --", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 764, "question": "Is it hard or easy to be with your own brother when you're making a record?", "qSentId": 763}, {"answer": "Yes, I have to say I'm pleasantly surprised because, because Donny and Marie is a big target.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 782, "question": "Are you pleasantly surprised?", "qSentId": 781}, {"answer": "I'm serious.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 785, "question": "Why do you say that?", "qSentId": 784}, {"answer": "I don't.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 790, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 789}, {"answer": "To be honest with you, I don't care anymore, because I am who I am.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 795, "question": "Why would you care what the rock audience think of you?", "qSentId": 794}, {"answer": "It's what you look like is unique to me.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 828, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 827}, {"answer": "Not every day.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 848, "question": "Every day?", "qSentId": 847}, {"answer": "I have never -- well, accidentally a couple times.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 852, "question": "Do you drink alcohol?", "qSentId": 851}, {"answer": "Never had a desire to take drugs, no.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 857, "question": "Never taken drugs?", "qSentId": 856}, {"answer": "Well, you know what, if that's what it takes to live a good life, yeah, call me squeaky clean.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 859, "question": "You are Mr. Squeaky clean, aren't you?", "qSentId": 858}, {"answer": "First of all, let me just make the statement, I think Lady Gaga is brilliant.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 867, "question": "-- sexuality, all that kind of stuff in their lyrics and so on, do you feel offended?", "qSentId": 866}, {"answer": "Marie, talk me through this.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 879, "question": "It's like who wants that kind of face?", "qSentId": 878}, {"answer": "I like that.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 893, "question": "Why don't we pretend you are?", "qSentId": 892}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, I lost 50 pounds.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 897, "question": "But what else do you do to keep in this kind of shape?", "qSentId": 896}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 901, "question": "Do you exercise?", "qSentId": 900}, {"answer": "Until the end of this year.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 905, "question": "How long are you going to be performing here, for starters?", "qSentId": 904}, {"answer": "There's all kinds of opportunities.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 910, "question": "Is there anywhere you'd rather be performing?", "qSentId": 909}, {"answer": "We just changed the show.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 918, "question": "When you finish up here, the shows -- because you're playing tonight -- what do you go out on?", "qSentId": 917}, {"answer": "May tomorrow be a perfect day", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 927, "question": "But the ones that we can't take out of the show is like -- what do we end the show with?", "qSentId": 926}, {"answer": "Well, sing me the song.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 941, "question": "How do you feel?", "qSentId": 940}, {"answer": "Wait.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 960, "question": "What are you doing?", "qSentId": 959}, {"answer": "It's just a tender side I hide so cleverly.", "docId": "110528pmt", "aSentId": 972, "question": "Is this the new side of you that we're learning?", "qSentId": 971}]